Add a 360 Image to Hotspot
将360度图像添加到热点
First, create a hotspot area and click “360-Degree Image Viewer” on the left
首先，创建一个热点区域，在左侧点击“360-Degree Image Viewer”
Return to the main menu and click “Media Library”
返回主菜单，点击“Media Library”
Select “360 Photos” and add a 360 image from your computer
选择“360 Photos”，从您的计算机中添加360度图像
Now return to the ETC configuration
现在返回到ETC配置
Add the 360 image you just uploaded to your library
将刚上传的360度图像添加到您的库中
You can also directly upload the 360 image from your computer
您还可以直接从计算机上传360度图像
Okay, now let's try the first display method: “Screen Overlay”
好的，现在让我们尝试第一种显示方法：“Screen Overlay”
Set the window size and let's start by placing the “anchor point” at the top left
设置窗口大小，首先将“anchor point”放置在左上角
Now, preview
现在，预览
Click on the hotspot area
点击热点区域
You can see the 360 image is at the top left, occupying half of the screen
您可以看到360度图像位于屏幕左上角，占据了半个屏幕
Let's go back and change the “anchor point” to the center
让我们返回并将“anchor point”更改为中心
Press Preview again
再次预览
Now the 360 image is centered
现在360度图像位于中心
Next, let's try the second display method: “Embed in Block Center”
接下来，让我们尝试第二种显示方法：“Embed in Block Center”
We resize the hotspot area, and click “Embed in Block Center” on the right
调整热点区域大小，在右侧点击“Embed in Block Center”
Press Preview
点击预览
Click on the hotspot area
点击热点区域
You can see the 360 image is strictly limited to the hotspot area
您可以看到360度图像严格限制在热点区域内
This is the “Embed in Block Center” method
这是“Embed in Block Center”方法
Now, let's try the third method: “Preset Display Window”
现在，让我们尝试第三种方法：“Preset Display Window”
First, create a new hotspot area and place it on the left
首先，创建一个新的热点区域，将其放置在左侧
Set it as a “Display Window”
将其设置为“Display Window”
Enter a “Display Window” name
输入“Display Window”名称
Press to confirm
按确认
Select the hotspot area and choose “Preset Display Window”
选择热点区域，选择“Preset Display Window”
Select the display window name you just added
选择您刚添加的显示窗口名称
Press Preview
点击预览
The 360 image is shown in the display window you created
360度图像显示在您创建的显示窗口中
Finally, let's try the last display method: “Embed Within Block Area”
最后，让我们尝试最后一种显示方法：“Embed Within Block Area”
Select “Embed Within Block Area” and define the window size and anchor point
选择“Embed Within Block Area”，定义窗口大小和“anchor point”
This operation is similar to the previously mentioned “Screen Overlay”
这个操作类似于前面提到的“Screen Overlay”
Press Preview
点击预览
The difference with 'Screen Overlay' is that the window is only shown within its own block area
与“Screen Overlay”的不同之处在于，窗口仅显示在其自身的块区域内
Now let's resize and change the “anchor point”
现在让我们调整大小并更改“anchor point”
Press Preview
点击预览
You can see the window has changed its position and size, but it still remains within the boundaries of its block
您可以看到窗口已经改变了位置和大小，但仍保持在其块的边界内